{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "f3c1f6e4-0f7e-4f94-8b2c-0d83a1bb53ea",
      "front": "Mangan",
      "back": "Makan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:50.734935+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "d99a4b0e-7797-46cb-ba0d-4f55c70d65d5",
      "front": "Turu",
      "back": "Tidur",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:51.293462+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "ee1b2a15-6f1e-4e04-b4a0-bd5c31192533",
      "front": "Mlaku",
      "back": "Berjalan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:51.852445+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "0088f217-522e-4455-8841-3f7c6ed39e8d",
      "front": "Lungo",
      "back": "Pergi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:52.303452+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "4dcd2521-feef-422d-ba63-5e1eb8b56a1e",
      "front": "Mlayu",
      "back": "Lari",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:52.665681+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "b4a4c8cb-2383-4f93-93fe-65e7034af389",
      "front": "Adus",
      "back": "Mandi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:53.029494+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "8b19f6c8-8f3d-4e9a-ab0d-ef4b7a4be3eb",
      "front": "Ngombe",
      "back": "Minum",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 2,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:59:53.277798+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "e55fa663-95c9-4de0-ae20-5a5538852f2b",
      "front": "Nyambut gawe",
      "back": "Bekerja",
      "interval": 3,
      "ease_factor": 2.65,
      "step": 4,
      "due": "2025-11-21T05:53:59.429446+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "3290d2ae-5048-49ba-8b5f-349bc0bd1421",
      "front": "Sinau",
      "back": "Belajar",
      "interval": 3,
      "ease_factor": 2.65,
      "step": 4,
      "due": "2025-11-21T05:54:01.421291+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "6b272b55-99a1-4a45-9e84-3ff4bd2b4a51",
      "front": "Nulis",
      "back": "Menulis",
      "interval": 3,
      "ease_factor": 2.65,
      "step": 4,
      "due": "2025-11-21T05:54:02.388103+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "8b72d8b0-b944-4204-82f6-3ee4e08d39d1",
      "front": "Macak",
      "back": "Berdandan",
      "interval": 3,
      "ease_factor": 2.65,
      "step": 4,
      "due": "2025-11-21T05:54:03.856623+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "28b97d2d-93b1-4a90-8fd6-5b16c9c63bfa",
      "front": "Nganggo",
      "back": "Memakai",
      "interval": 3,
      "ease_factor": 2.65,
      "step": 4,
      "due": "2025-11-21T05:54:05.220791+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "e5af0df5-74e3-4f31-ba34-77b15c3064f9",
      "front": "Woco",
      "back": "Membaca",
      "interval": 3,
      "ease_factor": 2.65,
      "step": 4,
      "due": "2025-11-21T05:54:06.375247+00:00",
      "first_time": false
    },
    {
      "id": "7d5c38f9-a9b6-4af7-98e7-eb48dc29057d",
      "front": "Ngerti",
      "back": "Mengerti",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "0d8b85c1-56f3-43fb-b11e-f7f54da82975",
      "front": "Njaluk",
      "back": "Meminta",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "7fa98adf-d8cb-4d9c-9258-5591468cc611",
      "front": "Maringi",
      "back": "Memberi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "3b9fe97c-b2b9-4a7d-b508-2fc979f8bb35",
      "front": "Aja",
      "back": "Jangan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "93f5df4b-902d-4ee5-aca3-22762c65e604",
      "front": "Kowe",
      "back": "Kamu",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "219d4bc9-0f45-44c4-82fb-34f4d2ebd854",
      "front": "Aku",
      "back": "Saya",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "28b9e3a1-f7f8-46da-b22b-eaf71eb57782",
      "front": "Omah",
      "back": "Rumah",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "061e2181-f4a1-4475-8d0b-2d91876c29ba",
      "front": "Pintu",
      "back": "Lawang",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "3237c65a-556c-4c98-9ca4-eb77e62a39e0",
      "front": "Jendhela",
      "back": "Jendela",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "3127a18d-bde1-4ed7-9ce8-f8d9e8d85dcb",
      "front": "Kursi",
      "back": "Kursi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "0cb4d1b6-a703-4f10-bd2d-296bf8ae5bc1",
      "front": "Meja",
      "back": "Meja",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "6bd8a3c3-5d40-4e0a-af07-fad93f95721a",
      "front": "Cahya",
      "back": "Cahaya",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "f4d5254d-0be0-4a6e-a5d0-792393b2c406",
      "front": "Kembang",
      "back": "Bunga",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "6de1835f-bd4d-441c-97c2-c81872232eac",
      "front": "Banyu",
      "back": "Air",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "68977be3-2f52-44a5-90e2-97c37bfcded0",
      "front": "Segara",
      "back": "Laut",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "de2fcbf1-60b3-4b0e-8d78-277a65557e35",
      "front": "Gunung",
      "back": "Gunung",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-20T05:53:23.894845+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    }
  ],
  "limit": {
    "new_limit": 7,
    "due_limit": 87,
    "init": [
      20,
      100
    ],
    "date": "2025-11-21T05:54:06.401466+00:00"
  }
}